Good afternoon and happy Monday. Thanks
for joining us. You're watching DProgram
with Ted R and John Kiryaku. Thanks for
being here.
>> How are you, Ted?
>> I have no idea if my camera is new and
improved. I just installed it while we
were doing the countdown, but we shall
see. Uh, so if anybody has any feedback,
positive or negative, please let me
know. Uh, I was told it would improve my
fuzziness.
>> It looks good, actually.
>> It does. Yeah, it looks good.
>> Okay,
>> now I'm on I'm on my phone because I
stupidly left my laptop across town, but
on my phone it looks crystal clear.
>> Well, you look good, you know, on your
phone. So, sometimes you look worse on
your laptop. So,
>> yeah,
>> who can tell, right? So, lots to talk
about today. Um, just as we uh open the
show, just the ABC just broke the news
that uh free speech hero and lion is
Jimmy Kimmel, the bravest social
commentator in American history, is
returning to the airwaves tomorrow
night. Woohoo. Uh, no, seriously, I was
against what happened to him. Um, and
uh, but you know, we don't really know.
We don't really know what the
discussions were between them. Um, you
know, we can speculate on that, but
anyway, that just happened. Uh,
obviously the big news of the day and
the week is the UN General Assembly here
in New York City. Uh, basically
everyone's recognizing Palestine. All
the cool kids, the not cool kids,
everybody is. And the Israelis are
freaking out and so is the United
States. Uh, the US is now thinking of
the Trump administration is considering
blanket sanctions against the
internationalbody.
It's like,
>> yeah, it's against
>> they're the ones who are supposed to
impose sanctions on you.
>> Yeah.
>> Hey, Ted, did you happen to catch Marco
Rubio's uh comments to the media uh
after the declaration of um of
normalization of relations with the
Palestinians this morning? He was trying
to be as threatening as he could be and
he was utterly unconvincing. He said
things like like he warned these other
countries that this was only going to
make the situation worse for
Palestinians and if they wanted to make
things better for Palestinians then they
shouldn't recognize Palestine. And it's
like buddy
how much worse could it possibly get?
like you are utterly completely totally
unconvincing
and it was obvious that this is just
what Netanyahu told him to tell the
press
>> that no Israelis are the thing is John
the Israelis are now threatening to
annex the entire West Bank like later
this week.
>> Yeah. You know what? Nobody gives a [__]
anymore
>> because nobody's going to recognize that
anyway.
>> Well, that's true. And the Israelis are
going to do what the Israelis are going
to do.
>> Exactly. and they've had plenty of time
to act decently and we know they're not.
So obviously we have to break down the
situation in the in Palestine. Um Tom
Holman uh he's uh it cames out that
basically it was like a I had John I had
like an abscam flashback. Uh he
literally took a bag a gunny sack of
$50,000
uh last fall before he was elected
anything before he was appointed
anything. Um, but basically he knew he
was going to be uh the you the uh
deportation zar for Trump if he was
elected if Trump got elected and he was
already accepting bribes ahead of time.
You have to assume that I mean of course
it was a sting operation but you you
have to assume that this guy is greedy
as hell. I mean dirty as hell.
>> Yeah.
>> And there's the H-1B situation. um which
I'm really I'm going to say here I I
come not to condemn Trump but to praise
him uh on this matter. So we could talk
about that too. Um and there's Kimmel
and there's other stuff and there's
always the questions from our brilliant
watchers. So what do you think John?
What should we do first?
>> You know I I would really like to um
address this Holman situation first if
you don't mind.
>> Oh yeah please.
>> Because like you
I was reminded immediately of ABSCAM.
Now, for those of our of our viewers who
don't remember ABS scam, this took place
in 1981
where FBI agents dressed up like Arab
shakes and bribed a US senator and
several members of the House of
Representatives. Of course, it was a
sting operation. Some of them went to
prison. All of them ended up being
heaved out of Congress. Uh but the
message was that bribery is wrong,
wrong, wrong. and you should not do it.
So now here we have Tom Holman who's the
head of Immigrations and Customs
Enforcement
and he's taking literally he's taking a
sack full of money
as a bribe.
It's caught on camera because it's a
sting operation
>> and President Trump said, "Oh, he didn't
do anything wrong. Leave him alone."
They're not asking that
that he resign.
>> And in fact, the president said today
his job is perfectly safe and he will
not permit the Justice Department to
file charges.
We're in the Twilight Zone. Ted, there
was another thing that's
similar that's parallel. Uh, you know,
Donald Trump has been saying for for
weeks, months, that he wants to
prosecute Leticia James and everybody
else, whoever did him wrong. Well, last
week, the US attorney for the Eastern
District of Virginia, which is the
Espionage Court, uh, resigned under
pressure from Trump. Trump now today
named a loyal Justice Department
official to be the new US attorney for
the Eastern District of Virginia. and he
has ordered her to prosecute Leticia
James in EDVA.
She can't
Leticia James is not accused of having
committed a crime in the Eastern
District of Virginia. There is no
connection to the venue. They can't do
it. But Trump said on Truth Social last
night that he has ordered the Justice
Department to begin uh to begin uh going
after arresting and prosecuting his
political enemies. He came right out and
said it
>> on True Social.
>> And so we're in uncharted waters right
now. We don't know where this is going
to go, if anywhere. And Congress hasn't
said anything. Nobody has the guts in
Congress to say anything. And then
today, the Supreme Court ruled that
Trump is allowed to fire the last
remaining Democrat on the Federal Trade
Commission. So all that does is it gives
the Republicans a very temporary win.
And it's a little incremental win. But
what the Supreme Court has done is
they've essentially said when the
Democrats win the White House, which
they will, they can fire all the
Republicans and put yes men in all of
their positions. So nice country our
leaders are giving us these days.
>> Well, assuming you're assuming the
Democrats would even have the balls to
inflict retribution, which there's very
little evidence of that. I mean, you
know, I mean, I I just, but I kind of I
mean, they won't. They might, but I
mean, you're right. They can, and they
would be tempted to, and there will
certainly be that discussion. I mean,
>> yeah. I mean, the Tom Holman thing is
disgusting. I mean, he was caught
unacceptable.
>> Dead to rights. Um, he's dirty. He's
corrupt. I'm not saying he should
definitely go to jail. Uh, you know, I
don't think they could convict him. um
you know because he wasn't holding
office at the time. So you know I mean I
can give you $50,000 if I want. You're a
private citizen. Why not? But I mean so
it's like a pre-bribe, a proto bribe.
But I mean but like we know but I mean I
would say it basically at the moment
that he took the that he that he decided
to I guess he sworn in to his duties as
uh you know the ISIS that he should have
been he should have told you know the
his bosses hey I gota this happened I
should give this back right.
>> Right.
>> I mean you would think I mean that's
what you or I would do.
>> Sure. Well I wouldn't have taken the
money in the first No. And if you're
going to take a bribe, you know, just
like we always used to say at the CIA,
if you're going to steal, don't steal
$20.
>> Steal $2 million. If you're going to
take a bribe and you're going to risk
not just your career and your
reputation, but your freedom, don't take
50,000 measly dollars.
>> Totally.
>> Millions of dollars.
>> No, for sure. I mean, these these guys I
mean, that's you know, my ex-wife used
to always say that about congressmen who
would be caught with like a $3,000
bribe. She would be like, "They're not
just [__] They're like crack [__]
They're cheap as shit." You know, you
can buy them off for nothing. I mean,
it's it's almost worse than the fact
that they're dirty is that they don't
they'll sell out their their civic
virtue for for nothing for pennies on
the dollar. Disgusting. Um I mean, well,
okay, I hesitate to ask this, John, but
Tom's Tom Hullman's gonna survive this,
right? Because the boss doesn't care.
>> No, I'm afraid he is. If if you don't
have a president who's going to put his
foot down and demand that you resign, if
you have a a a an attorney general who
will refuse to prosecute you or refuse
to allow you to be prosecuted, then
yeah, you've you've got no problems. But
then at the same time, see how many pegs
we fall on the United Nations um uh
corruption list for next year.
>> All right, questions. Import most
importantly, Rey Clovis is at his secret
undisclosed location. He'll be back
tomorrow. Um, okay. So, uh, Stephen
Victor Andrews outraged at how a
low-rated TV show got cancelled. I mean,
I was censored a dozen a dozen of times
over the years at the behest of the
official and unofficial government, but
I'm really worried about a TV guy. Uh,
okay. Ryan Jude, what's up with India?
Mostly Modi supporting India, Israel so
much. That is a good question.
>> Yeah, that's a good question. What does
Modi get out of it? I don't that I
actually can't answer. I understand that
Modi wants to take a step back from the
United States. Frankly, I would too if I
were Modi. Um, especially when he knows
that his bread is buttered by the
Chinese and the Russians and the
Brazilians and the South Africans and
the Iranians and everybody else that's
involved in bricks. But, but as to Mod's
closeness with Israel,
I have no explanation whatsoever.
>> And this question, I know I'm going to
giggle. Uh, and I shouldn't. Ef uh
Efuso.
So, thank you for the donation. Do you
think Kirk uh had superb bones? Was it
Jesus who made the bullet stay in Kirk
so no one else's got shot? Hashtag
miracle. So, for people who don't follow
social media, what this is about is that
the psychopaths who gathered yesterday
uh in in in Arizona to memorialize
Charlie Kirk literally, you know, it's
not enough for them to say that
literally he is a biblical prophet like
John the Baptist. Okay. Or or or Joshua
like like like Moses, an actual prophet.
Uh they said that over and over and over
yesterday. But some a lot of people in
MAGA world are saying that his the
bullet should have traveled through him
and then hit other people and that like
a savior like a like a soldier heroic
soldier throwing himself on a grenade to
save his buddy his extremely miraculous
Jesus body thickly prevented that from
happening.
Ted, did did you send me the the tweet
from the self-described prophetus?
>> Uh, no. I think that was Robbie.
>> Oh, was it Robbie? Yeah.
>> So, this self-described prophetist,
Unless Robbie wants to come on and and
>> Yeah. Hey, Robbie.
>> Put on your pants. Here we go.
>> There we go.
>> Pants are on.
>> Okay, fire away.
>> Tell us about the prophetus and what she
what she saw when she went to heaven
yesterday.
>> Uh, actually, that wasn't me. I I don't
know. Yeah. I I don't know about the
prophetus. Uh now I do have my own
questions about the ballistics, but I
don't know anything about
>> Let's do the ballistics and then we'll
do the prophetus.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Give us the
ballistics.
>> Okay. So, as someone who has done a lot
of shooting with a 3006 rifle,
>> the weapon used the weapon used to kill
Charlie Kirk.
>> Correct. Specifically mousers. I used to
have an old Argentine Mouser made in the
1890s. Beautiful gun. U if you shoot a
if you shoot one a a standard round at
200 yards, it's easily going over Mach 2
speed. That's just a that's one of the
reasons why that they used here in
Montana to take down big game. Now, the
question that I had was if they did they
release information on the bullet
because it seems like to me if you're
going to be doing this, you use a
hunting round because it's just be more
effective against against tissue.
Well, come to find out the government
hasn't released anything at all. They
haven't released an autopsy. They've
released ballistics on the bullet. And
instead I found out that they said that
this 306 bullet lodged up under the skin
which as someone who like I said who
does this stuff a lot before I started
losing my eyesight that does not happen.
If a 306 round hits a neckbone
it blows the bone out. I have seen this.
It works. What they're saying it makes
zero sense. And so the question that I
have is why is the government lying
about this? Because all you got to do is
just hop on Grock, hop on Google.
>> Well, it's not the government really
lying. It's government officials who are
basically playing the roles of who are
forgetting that they are government
officials, which is why they're engaged
in this partisan hackery uh that we saw
yesterday, but u basically just running
off with the mouth. They don't I mean
this is not an official, you know,
coroner's report or anything or a police
investigation or anything like that.
Yeah, nothing's been released, which is
wild because if they wanted to [__]
clamp down on sec on um
>> on conspiracy theories, I got just
release the report.
>> That's it.
>> I mean, I don't understand. I don't
understand why. I mean, they've got the
shooter supposedly,
so why sit on it? It makes no sense to
me.
Well, I mean, I think what's interesting
is like just the level of hysteria and
uh you know, just the the way that this
has been uh exploited. Uh it's so
insanely over the top. I mean, foolish.
I was reminded, I mean, of course, this
is one of my big controversies, but the
Pat Tilman um memorial service, uh,
which was also in Arizona, presided over
by warongering John McCain. Um, and you
know, he basically try they were trying
to same sort of thing, flags everywhere,
eagles everywhere, but I mean, they
didn't have the this one had it all. It
had fireworks when the widow walked out
on stage. I mean, you know, nothing says
class like like like fireworks. uh and
you know somber memorial service. I
don't know the whole thing. I mean the
aesthetics of it really deserve like a a
deep dive right I mean of of the event.
I mean about what it says. Um what was
really interesting to me was all the
discussion about like Charlie united
America at the same event where there
the people all the speakers are talking
about how half the country sucks and
killed Charlie Kirk. Um, you know, how
is there a uni? You you know, you can't
have vengeance and retribution and
unity. You got to choose.
>> I think that's pretty obvious which way
they've chosen. I mean, Trump himself
said that no, he hates his
>> I am your retri I am your retribution.
That's what he said before he was
elected. All right. Uh, Robbie, before I
take you out, u,
>> sure,
>> please remind everyone why they have to
go watch us on Rumble.
>> Yeah. So, there's a couple reasons why
you want to watch us on Rumble. want
part four of John's interview will be
releasing next month as a Rumble
exclusive.
>> That's a good one, too.
>> So, if you want to see that, come over
to Rumble. Uh, if you become a channel
subscriber for $5 a month, you can see
all the premium content on Deprogrammed.
Or if you want to see all premium
content across the entire platform, just
pay 10 bucks a month. That way, you see
that sweet, sweet boot gaming stuff,
too. Selfless self plug. Uh, also,
frankly, uh, Rumble pays a hell of a lot
more. And also, Rumble does not censor
the way that YouTube does. So, if you
want to have uh conversations about
ballistics and about what I think is
going on with Charlie Charlie Kirk, um I
don't think that shot in the neck that
we saw was a entrance wound. I think
it's an exit wound. I can't have that
conversation on Rumble or on I have we
can have that conversation on Rumble,
but on YouTube because YouTube will blow
us up. So, there is that. So, I'm going
to go away now and uh y'all keep on
going.
>> Thank you. You can take your pants off
now. Okay. So, um,
yeah. I mean, did you have a chance to
watch that, uh, that event yesterday or
excerpts?
>> I did.
>> What do you think?
>> I did. I thought it was um frightening
to tell you the truth.
>> It was frightening. Um,
there's a lot of anger, there's a lot of
hatred, there's a lot of division. Um,
and there are a lot of people in
positions of authority who believe a lot
of crazy things.
Oh, which brings me back to this
prophetus.
>> Oh, yes. Thank you.
>> So, this prophetus whose name I did not
I whose name I did not u recognize said
that she was taken to heaven yesterday.
God took her to heaven yesterday and she
saw God chatting with Charlie Kirk and
Charlie had wings
>> and God was talking to him
>> and God gave him a quiver full of arrows
and the arrows were made of light. There
were 1,000 arrows and they were made of
light and God told her to come back down
to earth and tell people that Charlie's
in good shape. He's in good hands.
[Music]
Dude, that's awesome. I love it. I I
mean, and the thing is,
what the [__] What was wrong with
people? And you know, there's going to
be people who who repeat this dutifully
like, "No, that's happened. He's with
He's He's hanging with God. I I saw
Holy shit." I don't know, man.
>> Yeah,
>> I don't know what to say.
>> Yeah. Well, all right. We were going to
talk about this, so we should might as
well talk about it. Rock Light, what's
our opinion on the H-1B visa fee? I was
surprised that there was no plan
announced with the implementation. Oh,
I'm never surprised when there's no plan
announced with the implementation.
>> I mean, planning isn't really Donald
Trump's thing. It's like, hey, draft up
the executive order. I assume they had
all the executive orders stacked up and
on a schedule before he took office. And
it's like,
>> yeah, usually they're written in the
period between the uh the election
inauguration.
>> Mhm.
>> I'm I'm convinced of that. It's like,
oh, it's September 22nd. Oh, this we're
doing this one. We're doing the H-1B
that day. Uh and they're all spaced out
very carefully. I'm convinced of that.
They're all stacked up. Uh but
>> yeah.
>> Okay. So they so so basically the H-1B
visa fee is very simple. If a company
wants to hire someone uh you know under
the H-1B program they have to pay the
federal government $100,000. So it's
very Trumpy. It's like well we also want
to get money you know. So in other words
it's not really about principle. It's
not really about hiring Americans. It's
about like you know it's about grifting
and bringing in some more money into the
treasury. But also, it is gonna it
obviously is going to discourage a lot
of of of people, a lot of companies from
doing these. They're saying that there
may be exceptions for doctors, which
frankly is a good idea. Um, but I got to
say, um, good for Donald Trump. I don't
say that very often, but I hate the H-1B
visa program. As a former uh as a former
engineering student, I know and have
heard and have read about countless
cases of people who are unemployed and
undermployed STEM workers, especially
people who got laid off in their 40s and
50s and can't get work who are
brilliant, who are American citizens and
then uh you know there's there's this
feeder that comes in from one pro one
you know basically the vast majority of
them are coming not only just from India
but they're coming through one company
in India to feed to feed Amazon and
Apple and Alphabet and all these
companies in Silicon Valley. Um they
they bring in these people, they work
them like dogs. They know that they you
know they can do that. They can underpay
them because otherwise, you know, if
they don't play ball, they get kicked
back and sent back to India and if they
don't want that, they're not going to go
along with it. Um, there's been
countless documented cases of American
citizens being told that they were being
laid off, but before they left, they
have to train their H1B visa
um, replacement. And for the record,
this program, according to to the law,
says it's only when an employer can't
find an American to do the job that they
have to go into they have to look
overseas. Um, you know, I was as a it
kills me to think that like as a if id
graduated with a physics degree, I might
have had to compete against someone who
is willing to take, you know, say 25%
less for the same exact job. It's
[__] I mean, as far as there's one,
as long as there's one American who's
either qualified or could be trained,
and that's an important point, could be
trained to do the job, I don't want
anyone, I don't want any H-1B visas
issued whatsoever. um if if they can't
find anyone and there's no no one's
smart enough in this country to do the
job uh who can be trained then okay fine
you you can look overseas that's my take
I have to agree with you and and I'm
thinking that despite the w the fact
that it was rolled out uh very
unprofessionally I think that the bottom
line is probably a good one um so many
of these tech companies love to hire
Indians and Chinese because they'll work
for a quarter of what an American worker
might command. And so if you make it
more expensive to hire the Indian or to
hire the Chinese or Taiwanese,
then um then maybe this is actually a
good thing for American workers.
>> I have to tell you the truth, I'm
willing to I'm willing to give Trump the
benefit of the doubt on this and see how
it plays out. But I think that on paper
it looks like a good idea. This is an
intersection between the progressive
left and and MAGA world. I mean, we all
I mean, Bernie Sanders, AOC, me, people,
we've all been complaining about this
for years. Um, and so this is a place
it, you know, it does show that there is
a possibility for left and right to get
together on some things. Question for
you, John, from Houdini. Did you ever
work with Marty? I don't know who that
is.
Mhm.
>> Okay,
>> Ted, forgive me. Um, my sound is
terrible. I'm gonna I'm gonna leave the
room and then come back in.
>> Okay.
All right. So, I will I will uh I will
hold down the fort for a little bit
while John leaves the room and then I'll
put him back in. Let's see what other
questions we have here. Of course, now
I'm not able Oh, there we go. Okay. Uh,
let's see. That's a John question. Oh,
Alicia wants to know who was the last
upstanding trustworthy president. You
know, I mean,
it's a little bit of a cliche. There's
John. All right, I'll put him back.
>> That sounds much better.
>> Oh, good. Good. We have a question which
is uh who was the least the last um
trust trustworthy president? And I was
about to say probably Jimmy Carter was
was probably fairly trustworthy.
>> Yeah. And I think Gerald Ford was
probably fairly trustworthy.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, not I mean, you
know, most of what they say is true. I
mean, least untrustworthy. I mean,
obviously
this we enough has been said about this
one, but I mean, God, I mean, Bush was
such a sack. Um, and uh, you know,
Andrew Johnson was I mean maybe he was
honest. He was just a turd. Um, you
know, when you get yourself impeached,
>> Lyndon Johnson.
>> Andrew Johnson.
>> Andrew. Yeah. He Well, he was drunk all
through the presidency.
>> And he was such a racist piece of [__]
that that was part of the reason that he
got impeached in 1868. I mean, when when
you get impeached for being too racist
by a bunch of other white dudes, rich
white dudes in 1860s, you're a racist
piece of [__]
>> You can say that again.
>> So, who was I'm sorry. At at the at the
1864 inauguration,
Andrew Johnson was so drunk that he
couldn't give his vice presidential
inauguration address. And afterwards,
Mrs. Lincoln said to to her husband
like, "You've got to be kidding me. This
was the only guy."
>> Yeah, it was bad.
>> It was hard to find good help. Um, did
John did you ever work with Marty? Who?
DD09 wants to know. Marty.
>> Yes, sir. Uh, Marty was my immediate
supervisor in uh, Alex Station. I And
and listen, I Marty and I were friends
from 1990. We served in We served in a
Middle Eastern country together.
>> How come he knows who Marty is? Who's
Marty? Like, why isn't that famous?
>> Marty's out there in the news now every
once in a while. We're talking about
Marty. Well, we're talking about Marty.
I'm not going to say because he's a
dick. He testified against me in the
grand jury in uh in 2012. And I I ran
into him about four years ago, and I I
said, "Marty, what the fuck?" I said,
"We were friends for decades, and you
testified against me in the grand jury.
you didn't even have anything to do with
my case. And he said, you know, I really
regret it, but they were just looking
for somebody to trash you and I was in
town and they pressured me. I was like,
shame on you, man.
>> What the [__]
>> Shame on you.
>> That's really lame. I was in town.
>> Yeah,
>> that's awesome.
>> They were just looking for people. They
were trying to get people together just
to trash me before this grand jury
because remember I um
I had uh been arrested in January of
2012, but I had not been indicted by a
grand jury. And my law is like, "What do
you mean you haven't been indicted?" And
I said, "No, there's not been a grand
jury." He said, "Oh, this is political."
My lead attorney, "This is political."
So, we made a motion to to throw out the
charges because I hadn't even been
indicted by a grand jury. And so, as
fast as they could, they called a grand
jury together. They got all my former
enemies from the agency to testify
against me over the course of four or
five days and then they indicted me and
they said, "Ha, now you're indicted."
I always had a great deal of respect for
Marty. He was one of the best, most
gifted, natural case officers I ever
met. But when it came time to show
honor,
>> he [__] you.
>> His was out to lunch.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh, thank you for the dollar donation.
Uh, couldn't agree more. Kirk's funeral
was right out of idiocracy. That's how I
felt.
>> It was weird, man.
>> It was Yeah, it's it I mean, these are
weird times. Um,
USX A-Rod, thanks for the donation. How
can the public trust any of the details
the FBI came out? Yeah. With um, it's
run by a buffoon. We'd rather release
select details and talk about Balhalla
than actually investigate.
>> He's right. How do we trust the FBI? We
can't trust the FBI.
>> No. No. Not. I mean, I think you could
run you could trust the agency writ
large maybe at one point, but yeah,
>> not with this guy. Um, Marble, why did
it take a genocide for the West to
finally recognize Palestine? Uh, I hate
to ask that question, but either they're
a state or not. I love that question.
>> That's a great question. That's an
important question.
>> Look, to me, this ca, this situation is
a lot like East Teeour. Um, and and I
used to have this conversation with my
father-in-law who was Taiwanese. He was
a big Taiwanese independence activist.
And he was like, "When are we when is
America going to give us our
independence? When are they going to go
to the Chinese and say, "Leave Taiwan
alone?" I'm like, "That's never going to
happen ever." I mean, first of all,
they're the Americans are selling too
many weapons and enjoying the the whole
split and they love using Taiwan to [__]
with China. This will go on forever. And
I was like, but I was like, if you guys
ever want your independence, you're
going to have to do like East Teour.
You're going to have to declare it and
then maybe, and he's like, but then the
Chinese will invade. I'm like, I don't
think so, but they might. And they might
kill a bunch of Taiwanese people. And
that's the price you pay for freedom. I
mean, that's that's what happens when
you are uh you know, when when when
you're fighting a much bigger power. And
I think what happened what's happening
with Israel is the same sort of thing.
The Israelis had to go to the mat in
order I mean they had to they had to
kill as many gazins as they possibly
could before and John I don't see you um
if your camera's off.
>> I see you. I see you.
>> There you are. So I felt like the um so
I mean I I think that basically the
world was never I mean Hamas was right.
The world didn't was not was moving away
from the Palestinian cause. They did not
care. They passed the Amazon, the
Amazon, the Abraham Accords. They were
going to completely throw the They threw
the Palestinians under the bus. The
Saudis were going to normalize relations
with Israel. No one gave a [__] Hamas
needed a gamecher and they made a game
changer. And you could argue about the
details and I have, but um I think it
required I mean to me the purpose of
terrorism is to ex you know is to expose
your enemy as monsters. So if you say
look the the Israelis and the Americans
are monstrous anti-Muslim oppressor
imperialist murderer [__] and then
you poke at them and you attack them and
you make them violently over-the-top
overreact or you prompt them to do so
then they've made your case for you and
that's I think that's what happened. I
think it was a October 7th was a huge
political success um for the
Palestinians and for Hamas
>> Palestinians. Yeah, I I agree. I think
that's that's exactly right. Um I you
know what I can't disagree with anything
you said. I I looked at a map in the
Washington Post today of countries
around the world that um that recognize
Palestine and countries that don't. And
you know, we talk about it here in the
United States like it's this really big
momentous decision that's going to
change the course of humankind. No, the
the countries that don't recognize
Palestine are the United States, Norway,
Sweden, Greece, Germany, and Austria.
And that's pretty much it. The rest of
the world has always recognized
Palestine or has for years. So, no, we
we make it sound like it's this
momentous
cataclysmic decision. No, it's not at
all.
>> Well, it's also everyone can read their
polls, right? I mean, recognizing
Palestine is probably the only popular
thing Emanuel Mcron has done in years.
>> Um, and uh, and look at and the latest
polls are out. the vast majority of
Americans at large, uh, not just
Democrats, now sympathize more with the
Palestinian cause than the Israelis. Uh,
by the way, about the magic bullet, um,
Turning Point USA executive producer
Andrew Kulvit says Broomhill claimed the
surgeon told him that Charlie's healthy
bones stopped the bullet. He also said
the coroner found it beneath the skin.
that I I just cannot
believe that any of that is true.
>> I don't
>> We saw the video. We all saw the video.
It did catastrophic damage to the man's
neck. It didn't hit a bone
>> in a in a tenth of in a hundth of a
second.
>> That's right.
>> Um
>> not a fringe leftist, but a mainstream
leftist murdered Charlie Kirk, says
Phil. All of the lies as he was a
racist, sexist, fascist Nazi were
literally a death warrant. Never mind
that they were all lies. Phil, I'm I'm
gonna agree. I'm not gonna look, I'm not
gonna to to break down the exact
specifics of Charlie Kirk's ideology.
Even if Charlie Kirk was a racist,
sexist [__] across the board, he
absolutely there's no that he did not
have that coming. But he wasn't. It's
true that like when I went back to to
look at um you know, he wasn't Mr.
Kumbaya, okay? He this is a guy who had
a hit list on professors that he wanted
to have fired because they were too
liberal from profess. So that's like
that's a fascist kind of thing to do.
But the point is overall he was kind of
a garden variety rightwinger and um I
don't think you know I mean it's true
that he would when you look for like the
the terrible racist stuff he was like
snotty about affirmative action. Hell so
am I. I hate affirmative action. I mean
you know it's like so whatever. I mean,
I agree. Uh, you know, I mean, I think
that's important. Um, anal ape wants to
know, it felt like, uh, like we were
heading towards a populist versus
establishment realignment away from left
versus right. That's why I loved John
agreeing 100% with Tucker since the
shooting. Left versus right got a boost.
Well, liberal versus conservative got a
boost.
>> Yeah,
>> I think the populist I think the
realignment's still there. It's just
waiting to come out after all this
madness. if this madness fades.
>> I I talked to Tucker yesterday about
this. He he had just gotten back from
Phoenix and and he told me that for the
very first time in his life, he
genuinely fears for the future of the
country. And and I said, I have to
agree. I I've never experienced this
kind of of hatred
>> amongst Americans before. I mean, you
know, we have we have political
>> stupidity.
>> Yeah. We have political problems and
issues and demonstrations and you know
think of think of the summer of 68 and
the the assassinations of Martin Luther
King and Bobby Kennedy but I've never
genuinely feared for the country like
today.
>> No, me neither. I mean we this is I mean
this is this is peak. We've gone full
[__] for sure here. Um so let's see.
Um Mel Michael Vilov wants to know wants
wants us to talk about France by ru
lasted less less than a week.
>> Yeah, I mean France is in real trouble.
Um you know congratulations
>> I did congratulations on uh Miss Emanuel
Macron. Look definition of insanity
doing the same [__] over and over.
That's what's going on here. I mean,
Macron was told in no uncertain terms by
the voters when he called the election
last year, the French voters want the
far-left and short or the far right, and
it's pretty close, right? The far left
is a little ahead of the far right. The
far right's a little better organized,
although last year it was a shining
moment for the left, but they don't want
centerright austerity [__] Nobody
wants that. And it he keeps coming back
with that over and over and over. The
French are are freaking out. This is
going to get ugly. We are going to see
May 68. I mean, it's it's France is
blowing up. And you know, I hate that
because France is my stop gap measure,
you know.
>> Yeah, I know, right?
>> In case of emergency. Ryan Jude, what
flavor of engineering were you asking
me? I'm a quality engineer. So I if id
graduated I would have been an applied
physicist and nuclear engineer. Um I
used to joke that like uh you know
Saddam Hussein would have loved to have
met me because I did know how to make an
atomic bomb.
>> Hey Ted, before we go on um I know
Robbie's telling us we have an ad and I
don't want you to miss it.
>> Okay Robbie, go ahead and pop that
sucker up there and I'll read it. Uh
John, you're a spiritual man. What makes
the prophetus claim any different than
any other theology? Good question.
>> Um, I just tend to generally think that
that everybody's nuts. You know, I I'm
I'm in Los Angeles right now. I'm
staying with my brother and my brother
is an an adamant atheist. I I even saw
he he wrote a check
like like I I didn't even know people
still wrote checks, but there's a check
on his on his kitchen counter to the
Freedom from Information Found Freedom
from Religion Foundation. Um
>> he just hates all all organized
religion. He wants to be active against
it. He thinks everybody's nuts. And you
know what? after after the Archbishop of
the Greek Orthodox Church threatened to
excommunicate me a couple of months ago.
I've been really sour on organized
religion.
>> Oh, I'm sorry. I mean, that's just one
[__] although he's quite an [__]
but here we go. Let's read this ad.
You've probably noticed Rumble is
growing fast and it's not slowing down.
They're building a real alternative to
big tech that puts creators first and
actually protects free speech. And now
there's Rumble Premium, an easy way to
upgrade your experience. With Premium,
you get ad free viewing across the
platform. No pre-rolls, no
interruptions, just the content you came
for. Plus, premium members unlock
exclusive content like bonus videos,
behind the scenes drops, and more from
your favorite creators. Right now,
Rumble is offering 10 bucks off an
annual subscription. Just go to
rumble.com/premium and use the promo
code studio at checkout. That's
rumble.com/premium. Promo code studio,
no ads, more freedom, and content you
actually care about. That's the deal.
Okay. Oh my god. So, we have so many
great questions. Oh, glad I can't see
the questions today because
>> Okay, don't worry. I'll pop them in
here. Um, Stevie, how considering the
low education levels in this country,
how can you expect to reasonably compete
with people from China and India that
have a far better education?
>> Good point.
>> It is a good point. And then, you know,
and maybe we'd have a higher educational
attainment level if we didn't make it
the most expensive product you can buy
be after buying a house. I mean, it's
literally a college education is at a
four-year school is 400 grand. Now,
>> I mean,
>> and let me add this now, and I'm going
to preface it. I'm going to preface what
I say by by saying that I'm neither
confirming nor denying that this is the
case. I'm just saying as an observation.
What kind of predicament does this put
the CIA in where the CIA wants Chinese
scientists to come and work in big tech
so the CIA can recruit them and send
them back to China
>> to then be
>> agents in place.
>> I wonder if Tulsi brings that up to to
the Donald.
>> I doubt
>> that's a good question though. That is a
really really good point, John. That
that would never have occurred to me.
This question is also for you. uh from
thief. You once mentioned talking to a
poppy farmer who talked about an
American in jeans telling him to grow
poppies. Can you talk more about this?
Are they CIA?
>> 1,000%. Yes. I probably sat in the same
in the same area of cubicles with
whoever it was who who told the guy. But
yeah, that was clearly a CIA officer
just like I I mentioned yesterday on a
podcast here in Los Angeles. Um there
there was a human rights an important
human rights like internationally known
human rights figure who told me that he
had a witness who was 12 years old at
the time of the 2001 Dashlei massacre in
northern um Afghanistan.
And what his new uh source was telling
him, the source was 12 years old at the
time of the massacre, was that at the
site of the massacre where 2,000 Taliban
soldiers were suffocated to death. Um
>> I've more than that.
>> Oh, it's bad. No, it was about 2,000.
That was all that the trucks could hold.
>> Uh but uh there were two men at the site
of the massacre wearing jeans and black
t-shirts and speaking English. So
>> and directing traffic. Who who could it
possibly be on November 30th and
December 1st, 2001 in Dashi Leyle,
Afghanistan, speaking English and
wearing blue jeans.
>> Yeah. I' I I met uh James Dolan, the uh
the uh the director of the film Afghan
Massacre, uh and talked to him
extensively about that. And like you
know, there's never been any
accountability from Obama had promised
to do something and he never did. Well,
may I may I talk about that for a
minute?
>> Yeah, let's talk about it. Because, by
the way, that I was, you know, I was
right there. That was like where I was
at that time.
>> So, Barack Obama said during the 2008
campaign that he was going to order an
investigation into the Dashi Leyle
massacre. What happened was on November
30th and December 1st, 2001, 2,000
Taliban soldiers on Mas gave up to the
Northern Alliance.
>> They were captured in Mazzari Shariff.
>> That's right. Missouri Sharif. So they
asked the CIA, "What do we do with these
Taliban?" And the CIA said, "This was a
Rashid Dustin project."
>> The the CIA said, "Truck them out to the
desert, hold them in the desert until we
can divide them up and send them to
smaller jails around the country."
Because there was no jail in
Afghanistan.
>> No.
>> That early on in the in the war that
could hold 2,000 people. As you said,
this was Abd Rashid Dostam, one of the
most vile, one of the darkest and most
murderous men in modern Afghan history.
>> I know. I I I had to I had to ask him
for a favor and uh I had to go to visit
him and it is it was it was it was weird
to say the least.
>> He said to me once, he said, "You don't
like me very much, do you?" And I said,
"No, sir, I don't. I think you're a
cold-blooded murderer." He sure [__]
was.
>> He laughed like that.
>> I mean, he literally was the guy. The
reason the Cabo looked the way it did
was him.
>> Yeah, it's exactly right. So, um,
they they trucked all these Taliban out
to the desert and
>> no water. One of the 14 survivors out of
the 2,000 said that when they opened the
trucks, the bodies fell out like
sardines from a can because there were
no air holes. There was no water. They
were screaming food.
>> They all suffocated.
>> And as Jokers, the New Northern Alliance
guys, some of them shot holes into the
tank into the shipping containers.
>> That's right.
>> Like, oh, you want some air here? We'll
give you some air.
>> Here's some air. and they just shot him
and killed them. I went up there in 2009
>> and you go to the site of where the
trucks were opened up and there are
human bones just all over the place and
clothing
>> just sticking out of the ground. It's
grizzly. So,
>> it's it's the killing fields of
>> very much very much so. So I told John
Kerry, I'm going to fly out to Mazeri
Sharif and uh I want to get to the
bottom of this. I know Abdasheed Dostam
did this and I believe that the CIA, if
it wasn't directly involved, the CIA
watched it unfold and did nothing to
stop it.
>> 100%. We even know the name of the unit
and everything.
>> Oh, sure. So I went out there.
>> I thought it was special forces had
something to do with it, too. uh that
that
wouldn't surprise me, but there were way
more CIA than there were special forces
at that point. So,
um I went out there and I came back and
I told Carrie, you know, there are human
bones sticking out of the ground and
they didn't even bother to bury to bury
the bodies. They just left them there in
the desert. So, I wrote a letter under
Car's auto pen signature to the CIA and
I said, "We have this witness that came
forward and I said, "Was the CIA
at the site of where the trucks were
opened?"
>> So, six weeks later, a colleague of mine
came into my office and said, very
casually, he said, "Hey, uh, the agency
sent you a response to your letter." And
I said, "I didn't see any response from
the agency. I just checked my mail an
hour ago." And he said, 'Well, they they
classified it top secret. And at the
time, I only had a secret clearance.
>> And I said, 'Well, what did it say? And
he said, um, it says, "Go [__]
yourself."
And that's essentially what it said.
They were like, "Who the [__] do you
think you are? We're not answering these
questions." And then that was that was
the end of it. So, I went to Carrie and
Carrie said, "You know, I think we
should probably just kill this
investigation."
And I thought, "Yeah, of course we
should because all you want is to be
Secretary of State. You don't give a
[__] about the truth."
>> Yeah.
>> It was on purpose.
>> Sure it was.
>> I mean, yeah. And it it was thousands.
Yeah. So these Taliban guys, right, like
they were the guys who couldn't catch
the the whole thing is so is so corrupt,
right? So the in the closing days of the
US invasion in the fall of 2001 for
people who aren't as familiar this with
this as you and I are so Kabell was like
the the last major thing to fall but
right before that the second to
important thing to fall was Mazzari
Sharif and when it did um there were
thousands of Taliban who surrendered
>> um and and and then the Bush
administration actually flew a lot of
them on planes over to Pakistan.
right? And release them,
>> right?
>> Um so, you know, like we weren't really
that serious about nailing the Taliban.
And my understanding is there were some
al-Qaeda guys there, too.
>> Well, remember, we were not at war with
the Taliban.
>> That's true.
>> We didn't have a beef with Taliban in
those early days. It was just al-Qaeda,
al-Qaeda, al-Qaeda, right?
>> And then there are these Taliban guys
getting involved.
>> So, they flew them away and they went to
they went to Pakistan, but not everyone
made the planes. in this, you know, the
the plane stopped running and uh it's
like the those who fell in ended up
packed inside the shipping containers
without any water, you know, and it it
can be well over a hundred degrees in
the desert in northern Afghanistan.
Hotter inside the shipping container,
I'm sure.
>> A lot hotter,
>> you know, they they baked in there. I
mean, it's it's like it's like a kid in
a car with the windows up. It's exactly
like that.
>> I'll never forget it. The guy said, the
kid said that they fell out of the the
shipping container like sardines from a
can.
>> Mhm. It's disgusting.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's one of the
biggest war crimes in US history.
>> Absolutely.
>> I mean, it's like been much bigger than
Mi, I think, in terms
>> in terms of sheer numbers.
>> Was what 35 people at MIund people,
whatever. We're talking about thousands
all at once.
>> Yep. Hey, uh, thanks for the, uh,
Mountain 16. Thanks very much for the
donation. This is a tourist question for
you, John. Hi from Mike and Nottingham.
Uh, John, my sister is going to Roads in
October. Great.
>> Any cool and interesting places there
you'd recommend?
>> Oh my gosh. Yes. Oh my gosh. Okay.
First, the most important thing is the
um is the crusader uh the walled
crusader town. It's it's calledapoli,
the old city, and it's in it's right
where the ships let you off, the cruise
ships let you off. So, it dates uh from
the 13th century, and it's one of the
most magnificent places in the world.
Number one, just outside the old city is
something that used to be called Monte
Smith, which is a colonial name. It's
now called the Acropolis of Roads and
it's a mountain that overlooks roads and
it has a temple of Apollo at the top of
it. Magnificent view. Then if you go
down, there are three ancient cities of
roads. There's Lindos, Yalisos, and
Gamos. So Lindos is on the east coast.
Don't miss Lindos. It's probably the
most beautiful spot on the entire
island. And there's a magnificent
acropolis. Uh so it's walled and then
there's a temple of Athena up there,
Lindian Athena. Um the other two ancient
cities, one is my my paternal um uh
village.
Uh Gamos is a little bit inland. So
Lindos, the ancient city was at the top
of the mountain. Gamos, the ancient city
was going up the mountain. And you can
go tour the ruins and there's a
wonderful museum there. our village,
Yalis,
they know they know that the that the
the ancient city was there somewhere.
And then every few years, a 2500y old
statue will wash up on shore. So they
know it's there. They can't quite
exactly find it. But that's that's what
you want to do in roads.
Yalisos and Camos and the village of
Monolithos which has that's where the
word monolith comes from and it's got a
castle at the very top of the monolith.
Uh and then on the east coast Lindos but
the the old city of roads is absolutely
magnificent. You can just get lost
wandering around the the cobblestone
streets.
>> Okay. Um, question. Um, what would Oh,
let me There was Oh, yeah. I like this
one. Brun, what's the deal with, uh,
exal Qaeda Akmed Al-Shara coming to the
US to meet with Mr. Little Marco Rubio?
Um, it's uh, Petraeus even sat down with
them and said he was a fan.
>> Yeah.
>> Well, it's not the first time we've ever
dealt with radical uh, head chopping
Islamists, right? I would put money
on the notion that he was a paid CIA
agent that he has been for a long time
and they've brought him in from the cold
and they made him the president of
Syria.
>> I would I would buy that 100%. Yeah. I
mean the Free Syria army, right, which
then morphed into the al-Nusra front
which then morphed part of it moved
morphed into ISIS.
>> Yeah. Lovely people. I mean it's it's a
replay of what we did in Afghanistan,
right? I mean
>> it's exactly the same playbook.
>> It's um what do you think about the
theory from Zaryi Denoon um about the
theory that Israel is being so hostile
because their religion states that
Israel will eventually fight against the
whole world and then God will save them.
>> I think there are a lot of Messianic
Jews who believe that that is exactly
what we're at the beginning of right
now. And I think there are a lot of
evangelical Christians who agree and who
actively support it. There are a lot of
evangelical Christians in the United
States who believe that they can hasten
the return of the Messiah
by helping the Israelis to attract Jews.
>> But then all the all the all the Jews in
Israel get killed, right? They're like
moths to the flame. Yep.
>> They all they're all in one place
conveniently to be killed,
>> right? That's if I'm if I'm Jew if I'm
Jewish. I'm like, this is not a I don't
know if I want to play along with this
particular scenario.
>> That is the prophecy
>> question. I think we you should answer
this one, too. Do you believe MAGA is a
fascist movement? And if so, do you
think violent resistance against fascism
is warranted?
>> I you know, I I actually don't think
MAGA is a fascist movement as a
movement. I think it's a populist a
right-wing populist movement, but I
think that MAGA leaders are turning it
into a fascist movement.
>> That's well said. I think it has I I
mean I think it there are it it's the
it's the clay that can be turned into a
fascist movement.
>> There it is right there.
>> Um it's it's like and certainly there
are some fascist aspects to it. Uh, but
it really I mean this was basically was
just the Tea Party that got funneled
into the Trump campaign. But you know
once you see everyone wearing the same
hats and going to big rallies and s and
and basically cheering on the leader no
matter what outlandish stupid [__] that
they know isn't true and can't be true.
Um, you know, once you're talking about
like uh scapegoating uh the non-existent
enemies, right? I mean this situation
with the radical left and cells are out
there. That's Emanuel, you know, Emanuel
Goldstein from 1984, right? There was no
resistance. So the party made it up and
and like that's that's made up. There is
no if there was a rad radical
resistance, I would have signed up with
them years ago.
>> But okay, that said, is are we in danger
of fascism coming to America? Never have
we been closer.
>> Oh my god. I so agree. I so agree. And
what makes it that much more dangerous,
Ted, is that it's so incremental. Like
literally every day you and I
>> Yeah. We get these push notifications
every day. The the Supreme Court allowed
this to stand. The Supreme Court allowed
that to stand. There's a new uh Trump
executive order that's, you know, doing
this thing or that thing or the FBI is
going to do this or the US attorney's
doing that. It's like it all adds up to
fascism. Well, this is very similar to,
you know, after Hitler was elected in
1933. It took nine months before or so
before um the Reichto passed the
Enabling Act and that was like the final
death nail for German democracy. Um, and
I mean I, you know, I was talking to
Scott Stantis, my friend and colleague
at the Chicago Tribune about this, uh,
this morning, and he said, you know,
Trump's a little slower. Um, you know,
it's it's like it's going to take three
months longer. But he's like, I wouldn't
be surprised if the Republican Congress
passed a law that said anything that
Donald Trump wants is automatically the
law. Or I mean, and at that point,
fascism is here or totalitarianism is
here anyway. maybe not fascist
traditional fascism because you really
have to have rampant militarism and
invasions of foreign countries which
Trump fortunately doesn't seem to be
that into. Um but I mean and look I'll
answer the tough part of the question
which is you know is armed resistance
justified to resist fascism? Yeah, armed
resistance is justified to resist
fascism. My grandfather was in the
French resistance so yes it is.
You know, my grandmother, my mother's
mother
was um she was in Greece in 1940 when
the Germans came in and um and she was
arrested and put in in prison only
because she was an American citizen, not
for any other reason. And she was young.
She was only 21 years old. And um
and my grandfather was able to get her
out of prison by bribing a Nazi prison
guard with American magazines. And then
they got onto a a steamer and went back
to the United States. And it was only by
the grace of God that they were able to
get out. So
>> that's insane.
>> We're not all going to be so lucky the
next time this happens. And hopefully
I'll stay out of prison long enough to
revel in the fact that John, we are
currently ahead of Fox News on Rumble.
>> Oh my god.
>> We're on the front on the front page. We
are number eight in America.
>> Wow.
>> Live.
>> Wow. Wow. Wow.
>> Our little show.
>> That is absolutely wonderful. Thank you
everybody. Thank you. And also big thank
you to uh Olanos just gifted five
subscriptions to the show.
>> Wonderful. Wonderful.
>> Scary girl. Much much deserved. Like
glad to see her get that. Ryan Jude,
thank you. So, uh thank you so much for
that. That's amazing.
>> So, all right. So, let's talk about um
what comes next. I mean, by the way, did
you hear Netanyahu late last week talk
about?
Yes.
>> So yeah. So Netanyahu realizes I mean
he's a lot of things you know the devil
but he's but he's not stupid and he can
see the direction that this is all
going. So people have been asking me
what's the practical direct um impact of
the statehood um you know declaration
none. But the point is that the word is
now out that it's not cool to hang with
Israel anymore. So big business isn't
going to want to do business with them
anymore. there won't be contracts. They
won't be able to import or export. They
won't be able to recruit people or send
their people overseas um to work and and
send money back. So basically, Israel is
going to find itself more isolated than
South Africa did under a parttheide. And
frankly, they deserve it because their
behavior, their conduct is even worse
than South Africa during a parttheide. I
mean, at least the South Africans
weren't just systematically butchering
hundreds of thousands of people just for
fun to steal their land. Um, so the, um,
so now you've got, um, but I think
what's going to happen is it's true. Um,
BB is literally thinking, we're going to
have to have autarchy. We're going to
have to be completely independent. And
I'm thinking, okay, the last time anyone
said that was Paul Pot. Uh, he was like,
we don't have to deal with anyone. At
least at least Campuchia was
agriculturally rich, right?
>> Okay. I mean, yeah, I like I like I like
the the wines from the Golan Heights,
but they don't have that much there. I
mean, I don't see how this works. I
think Israel will collapse. I mean, I
think, you know, we're not going to have
a negotiated settlement. I think the
economy of Israel will collapse and we
might the and it'll be a postapartide
type scenario. They're just going to
have to say uncle and and and just
somehow work it out with the
Palestinians because their economy will
be dead. See, but I think maybe I'm
maybe I'm expecting a lot worse, but I I
don't think they will give because I
think they
>> I I I think they would rather nuke
themselves and everybody around them
>> rather than rather than to be destroyed
from the outside.
>> I think they're honestly I think they're
they're like a rabid dog. I mean, I
think they need to be put down at this
point. I mean,
This is ridiculous. I think the world
should invade Israel and take it over.
>> Yeah.
>> I mean,
>> and administer it. Yes.
>> Yeah. I mean, I don't know how you
secure the nukes.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> Um, so, uh, let me put Rob Robbie back
on. He has a question here. All right.
Here we go. Robbie,
>> howdy.
>> Yep. So, no, we've had a couple of
people on YouTube ask how they are able
to donate. The short answer is you have
to come you have to come to Rumble
because YouTube pulled the ability for
people to donate using super chats. Uh
they gave me a BS reason that does not
hold water because up until about a week
ago uh people are able to donate and
YouTube is now playing games. So if you
want to donate to John and Ted go to
Rumble. I just shared a link over on the
YouTube chat and frankly uh Rumble also
pays them significantly better. So watch
them over there. you can donate and also
you can support the show and just by
watching which is huge.
>> So thank you.
>> I think maybe we we we you know what
we'll do is we'll create a PayPal
account and uh we'll we'll we'll put
that up so people can donate and thank
you by the way. Oh my god. Thank you so
much for for that. Uh for your support
is just amazing. Um you guys. So
>> So yeah. No, John, I could see them I
could decide I could see them deciding
to you know basically take us out with
>> everybody. Yeah. Take everybody down.
And Ted, I know
>> they don't have ICBMs, though.
>> Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I I know that
we're running short on time and I don't
want us to to miss what's arguably the
most important story of the day that
apparently Robert F. Kennedy Jr. has
cured autism.
>> Did you see this?
>> I did. He said just by telling us not to
use Tylenol.
>> Yeah. It's like don't take Tylenol, but
take lots of vitamins instead. Who knew?
>> Who knew?
>> And and the president said yesterday
that in the next couple of days he's
going to come out with the announcement
about the cure for autism. It's just to
take vitamins.
>> You know, if only if only the parents of
autistic kids
>> knew about vitamins.
>> I know.
>> I mean, I bet they're they don't have
>> Yeah, but the thing is where you find
vitamins, they're impossible to find.
Oh, no. Wait a minute. They're not
impossible to find.
No, no, they're out there.
>> Oh, this is a great question. David
Galvin. Okay. Well, we should talk about
the the We'll talk We'll talk about
David's question in a sec, but RFK Jr.
is the biggest [__] disappointment to
me.
>> I was going around telling everyone on
air and off air, like the only the thing
only thing I was really happy about
Trump besides the possibility that he
was going to lift sanctions against
Russia so we could get back to work um
was the fact RFK Jr. like make America
healthy again, get rid of of additives
and preservatives from our poisoned food
supply, uh you know, cleaner food, adopt
the EU standards, you know, all those
things are great. And it's like,
>> we didn't get any of that crap.
Basically, all of his critics turned
out, I admit, I was wrong. All his
critics said he's a [__] maniac. He's
a nut. He's an antivax psycho. And that
turned out to be true. Mhm.
>> I made a fool of myself repeatedly by
saying that I consider him to be a
friend, right? We were very friendly
before his presidential campaign. And
then and then Dr. Aaron Good, who was a
frequent uh guest on the show that I had
with Michelle, would say, "Oh, he's
great. He's great. He's great. I'm
joining the campaign." And then he quit
the campaign. And Aaron said, "No, he's
nuts."
>> And I thought, "Oh, well, no, he's not
nuts. Aaron probably had some kind of a
runin with him or whatever." No, Erin
was was right. He's nuts.
>> Yeah, he's nuts.
>> He's dangerous.
>> Yeah. Every what the liberals what the
Democrats said turned out to have been
true about him. It sucks. I hate being
wrong like this. Yeah, me too. Greg Greg
Palace like threw him under the bus and
said like, you know, that brain worm got
my friend. We used to be close friends.
They used to work together all the time.
I you know, I love Greg and um and I
worked with Greg on his on a couple of
his books and I would again in a second.
So, Greg, if you're watching, you know,
operators are standing by. Um, and so
when I when I read this harsh commentary
from Greg, I was like, "Holy [__] I
hope he never gets mad at me. I mean,
that that sucks." And I was like, "Poor
Bobby. What did he do?" Like, and then
now I'm like, "No, Greg was right. He
just saw it before I did."
>> Yeah. Yeah. I hate to say I was wrong,
but I was wrong. Big time wrong.
>> Two very related questions, so I'll read
them at the same time. David Galvin, do
you think the mega movement would push
back on if Trump started to become a
dictator like the fall of the Democratic
Party to nothing and the fall of the
legal system and the courts? In other
words, if he became a dictator and Paris
s a hypothetical question, if Israel
were well, this is not related. It were
to collapse, could you see a coup coming
to stop Netanyahu and the lunatics?
Well, they are related questions, right?
So, in other words, if we get complete
manic insane fascism in Israel and in
the United States, could we see the
locals uh rise up and, you know, a
revolution?
>> I I would say yes. It would have to get
bad enough, but yeah, I I would think
so. Yes. And you know what? I wouldn't
be surprised to see the leader of that
revolution come out of the Pentagon,
>> right? Well, that would be Yeah. I mean,
it's true. often, you know, as we saw in
the Russian Revolution, right? I mean,
it's when the military signs up that's
like that's often the last piece, right,
that they're the ones who close the
deal, but they kind of need to see that
the people they they don't want to they
usually take orders until they stop
taking orders.
>> Yeah. Right.
>> Um I don't God, I hope we don't get to
that point.
>> God, I can't.
>> It is a long [__] way to 2028,
though.
>> Yeah, it is. I mean, yeah, right now I
can't even, you know, it's like I can't
just hold my breath. Oh, it'll be gone.
I mean, we'll be in the campaign cycle
soon. There's not going to be even pre-
campaigning until like late 2027. Um, so
we got to get through two and a half
hard [__] years. I don't know.
>> I agree.
>> So, in the meantime, we will continue to
deprogram you as long as they'll allow
us to do that. Um, and we'll, yeah,
we'll work on that PayPal thing and, uh,
put that up. And thank you so much for
the donations you guys were able to do.
Please like, follow, and share the show.
The drogram show with Ted Roll and John
Kuryaku is here Monday through Friday at
5:00 PM Eastern time. Uh, and we will
therefore be back tomorrow, Tuesday, at
5:00 PM Eastern. See you then. Thanks,
Robbie West. Go check out Robbiey's
gaming channel, Putinbot Gaming. Buy my
book. I'm not going to put up the cover
today. Uh, what's left by John's book.
What's the latest book called?
>> Uh, it's called Remains of the Day. It's
coming soon.
>> Can you pre-order it?
>> Four weeks.
>> Is it pre-orderable?
>> Should be up in the next week or two.
>> Excellent. All right. Well, we'll keep
an eye on that. Okay. Bye all.
>> Bye.
Huh?
>> Hey. Hey.